oneida.com 2009-06-15

# Oneida Customer Service Privacy Policy

  * Return Policy
  * Terms of Use Policy
  * Privacy Policy

* * *

**Oneida Privacy Policy:** **Your privacy and Oneida.com:  
** Oneida respects your privacy and is committed to protecting you while on our site. We have developed this privacy policy to explain our position on privacy issues and how they relate to the use of Oneida.com.

**How we use email:  
** When someone opts-in to receive emails from Oneida, we will use email as a method of communication with our customers to announce special events and promotions, product-related announcements and contest winners. Oneida does not sell or share email address information with any 3rd parties.

 **Cookie files:**  
Oneida.com uses files called cookies to track user sessions on our site. A cookie is a small file placed on your computer from a web server containing a unique ID for your computer. Cookies enable us to customize your shopping experience and provide you with relevant content and offers. The cookie file does not contain any personally identifying information, and cannot control or access your computer or files located on your computer.

**Collection of personally identifying information:  
** When you place an order at Oneida.com, all personally identifying information (Name, Email Address, Address, Credit Card Number) is submitted via secured connection, and stored in a controlled, limited access environment. The information that we collect in this manner is required to fill your order.

**Oneida will also ask for information in site surveys to assist in market research, product development and site design:**   
This information is analyzed in aggregate to determine consumer trends and to obtain feedback on the functionality and appeal of our web site. 

**The Oneida Patterns for a Lifetime enrollment form:  
** This form requires basic personally identifying information, which enables us to contact you about your Patterns for a Lifetime pattern. 

**How we use information we collect:**  
If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive catalog mailings from Oneida, Ltd. regarding new products and services. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, please let us know by clicking here to complete the " **Do Not Mail**" form or by calling us at 888-263-7195

Occasionally, we may establish a relationship with certain companies that perform consumer networking functions on our behalf. This would enable these reputable companies to communicate with you for promotional purposes that may be of interest to you and your needs. These companies have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the data. They are restricted from using this data for other purposes, and in any way other than to provide the requested services to Oneida, and may not alter or resell the data.

**Checkout** :  
Although our checkout procedure requires you to provide an email address in order to process your order, you may opt out of receiving future emails from Oneida by un-marking the opt-in box located below the email address section during checkout. 

**User submitted content:**  
Oneida Ltd. reserves the right to edit “Gift Message” comments for form and content. 

**Questions and comments:  
** See the Contact Us section if you have any additional comments or questions. We are always happy to answer your questions and listen to your thoughts and suggestions. 

**Oneida reserves the right to alter our privacy policy at any time:  
** Any revisions or additions to our privacy policy will be posted here for public viewing at least ten days prior to their effective date.
